<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Markdown on Ming Muay Thai</title>
    <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/tags/markdown/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Markdown on Ming Muay Thai</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mingmuaythai.com/tags/markdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kids&#39; Muay Thai</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/kids-muay-thai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/kids-muay-thai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Exciting &amp;amp; Fun Muay Thai Classes for Kids!&#xA;A lively Muay Thai class for children aged 8–14, where they can stay active, build fitness, and learn real martial arts techniques with punches and kicks. Classes use the same punch bags and Thai pads as the adults, combining safety, fun, and skill development. Perfect for all levels!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 on 1</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/1-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Personal one-on-one training sessions with a professional coach tailored to your specific fitness goals, technique improvement, or rehabilitation needs. Whether you want to build muscle, lose fat, or correct posture, we guide and motivate you every step of the way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To begin one-on-one training, please &lt;a href=&#34;https://mingmuaythai.com/#contact&#34;&gt;contact coach Ming or coach Mannie&lt;/a&gt; to discuss your individual training needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note that 1 on 1 training incurs additional payment not covered as part of any general membership package&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Clark Wins Fight at Shock &#39;n&#39; Awe 38</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/tom-wins-sna-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/tom-wins-sna-38/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ming Muay Thai fighter Tom Clark defeated Farouk Vahdati in a thrilling &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/K-1&#34;&gt;K1&lt;/a&gt; bout in Portsmouth on 15th March 2025.&#xA;Tom maintained his steely composure throughout the three rounds, keeping the fight on his terms.&#xA;He allowed Farouk to tire himself out, and inflicted damaged in short calculated bursts before moving back to safety.&#xA;Between rounds Tom looked relaxed and rested before launching back in and putting his mark on the fight.&#xA;Tom won the fight by unanimous judges decision at the conclusion of three rounds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Fitness</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/core-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/core-fitness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Core Fitness focuses on strengthening your abdominal, lower back, and stabilizing muscles to improve posture and functional strength. Targeted exercises enhance your body’s balance and stability, helping prevent injuries and providing a solid foundation for both daily activities and athletic performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIIT</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/hiit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/hiit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;High-Intensity Interval Training (HIIT) combines short bursts of intense exercise with recovery periods to maximize fat burning and improve cardiovascular health. This efficient workout helps you achieve optimal fitness results in less time, boosting calorie burn and enhancing heart and lung capacity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muay Thai</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/muay-thai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/muay-thai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professional Muay Thai technical training focusing on punches, kicks, elbows, knees, defense, and footwork. Enhance your power, speed, and coordination while building a strong body and confidence. Suitable for all skill levels to progress steadily.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muay Thai Fitness</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/muay-thai-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/muay-thai-fitness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Muay Thai Fitness is a high-energy full-body workout that combines authentic Muay Thai techniques with cardio and strength training. It boosts your endurance and coordination while burning up to 800 calories per session. Every punch and kick is delivered with power and rhythm, helping you sculpt a strong physique while releasing stress and energy—making fitness both enjoyable and challenging.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muay Thai Sparring</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/muay-thai-sparring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/muay-thai-sparring/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Safe and controlled sparring sessions where you apply your skills in realistic ring scenarios. Sharpen your reaction speed and strategic thinking, push your limits, and experience the true thrill of combat.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yoga –  Gentle Release Stretching</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/yoga-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/yoga-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Soft, mindful stretching to relax muscles and encourage recovery, perfect for post-exercise or during stressful times.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yoga – Deep Stretching</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/yoga-deep-stretching/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/yoga-deep-stretching/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Long-held deep stretching poses target deeper muscle layers, enhancing joint range of motion and overall flexibility. This helps prevent injuries and improve athletic performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yoga – Relaxing &amp; Flexibility Stretching</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/yoga-flexibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/yoga-flexibility/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gentle yoga classes help release body tension, improve flexibility and mobility, and reduce stress, allowing you to find balance in a busy lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Website is Live!</title>
      <link>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/live-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mingmuaythai.com/posts/live-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our new website is live. We are looking forward to sharing the exciting news about Guildford&amp;rsquo;s newest Muay Thai fitness and competition training gym.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
